League of Women Voters of Albany County; Records apap128
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1940-2001; 7; 7.77 cubic ft.
  - National LWV, 1940-2001; 7.2
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Post-Board Summaries, 1998-1999 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Presidential Accountability, 1975 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Recycling is More Than Collections, 1991 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Strategies for Effective Public Involvement: Drinking Water Source Assessment and Protection, 1998 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Tackling the Trouble with Trade -- From Tashkent to Topeka to Tokyo, 1973 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Talking Trash: A Citizen Education Guide for Community Leaders and Activists, 1993 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Tell it to Washington: A Guide for Citizen Action Including Congressional Directory, 1983-1984; 1993-1994; 1999-2000 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund The Citizen and the Budget Process: Opening Up the System, 1974 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund The Federalist Papers Reexamined Series, 1977 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund The Women's Vote: Beyond the Nineteenth Amendment, 1983 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund A Time for Choosing: The Role of Foreign Aid in U.S. Policy, 1987 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Tools for Drinking Water Protection: Leader's Guide, 1997 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Transporting Radioactive Spent Fuel, 1996 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Troubled Cities: Roots, Realities, Remedies, 1980 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Understanding Economic Policy: A Citizen's Handbook, 1990 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Unfinished Business: State Legislators on Monitoring the Executive Branch, 1974 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund U.S. National Security: Facts & Assumptions, 1983 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund What Ever Happened to Open Housing? A Handbook for Fair Housing Monitors, 1974 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Wired for Democracy: Using Emerging Technology to Educate Voters, 1995 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Great Idea, 1946-1980 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
      25 Years of a Great Idea, 1946, 40 Years of a Great Idea, 1960, 60 Years of a Great Idea, 1980.
    - 75th Anniversary Commemorative Journal, 1920-1995; 1995 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Agenda for Security, 1988 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 40)
    - "A Great Idea...", Brochures, 1984 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 41)
    - A Report to the Nation, Undated (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Art of Raising Money, How to Raise Money, 1954; 1964 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Board Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Board Reports, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Board Reports, 1964 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Board Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Board Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Board Reports, 1972; 1974; 1976 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 49)
    - "Brief for Action: The International Trade Organization", 1949 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Carrie Chapman Catt: The Power of an Idea, 1958 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Choosing the President, 1964; 1968; 1972; 1976; 1980 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 52-53)
    - Citizens Handbook: Answers to Frequently Asked Questions, 1986 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 54)
    - DHR Newsletter, 1968 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Developing Program: Fresh Approaches, 1979 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Diversity Toolkit, 1999 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Empowering Citizens: A Guide to Influencing Public Policy, 1996 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Facts About the League of Women Voters, 1951-1982 (not inclusive) (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Facts and Attitudes on World Trade, Undated (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 60)
    - Freedom Agenda Series, 1954-1955 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 61-62)
    - Foreign Aid at the Crossroads, 1966 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 63)
    - Foreign Economic Policy: Building Regional Stepping Stones to Economic Growth, 1962 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 64)
    - Government in Action: A Course for Training Civic Leaders, 1961 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 65)
    - Hard Choices: The Realities of Economic Development at Home and Abroad, 1960 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 66)
    - Impact on Issues, 1976-1982; 1984-1988 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 67)
    - Impact on Issues, 1984-1988 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 68)
    - Impact on Issues, 1994-1996; 1998-2002 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - In League, 1980; 1989 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - In Perspective, 1920-1995; 1994 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - In Touch: The League in Action, 1990; 1991 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Is Politics Your Job?, 1966 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Know Your County, 1946; 1962 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Know Your Town Government, 1952 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Leadership for Effective Leagues, 1958 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - League Connections, 1999 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - "League of Women Voters Tries Harder", 1969 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Local League Handbook, 1955; 1956; 1962; 1969 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - "Meaningful Meetings: The Role of the Resource Committee", 1976 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - MEMO Series, 1945-1946; 1948; 1951-1953 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 13-14)
    - L.W.V. Memorandum, 1985 March 9; 1985 August; 1987 December (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Mr. Congressman...His Moneybags and Watchdogs, 1953 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Mr. Madison's Constitution and the Twenty-First Century: A Citizen's Discussion Guide, 1988 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
    - "National Continuing Responsibilities", 1957; 1959; 1960; 1962; 1966 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
    - The National Voter, 1951-1953 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - The National Voter, 1954-1956 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - The National Voter, 1956-1960 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - The National Voter, 1961-1963 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - The National Voter, 1963-1965 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - The National Voter, 1966-1968 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - The National Voter, 1969-1971 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - The National Voter, 1971 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - The National Voter, 1972 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - The National Voter, 1973 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - The National Voter, 1974 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
    - The National Voter, 1975 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
    - The National Voter, 1976 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
    - The National Voter, 1977 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
    - The National Voter, 1978 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
    - The National Voter, 1979 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
    - The National Voter, 1980 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
    - The National Voter, 1981 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
    - The National Voter, 1982-1984 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
    - The National Voter, 1985-1986 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
    - The National Voter, 1987-1988 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
    - The National Voter, 1989 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 40)
    - The National Voter, 1990 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 41)
    - The National Voter, 1991-1993 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 42)
    - The National Voter, 1994-1995 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 43)
    - The National Voter, 1996-1997 (Box 30 (7-Publications), Folder 44)
    - The National Voter, 1998-1999 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - New Perspectives in Foreign Policy, 1958 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - New Trends in State Finance, 1973 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - On the Record: Congressional Votes on Issues in 1950s, Undated (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - On the Water Front: Water Resource Development, 1957 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - "Pick a Candidate", 1976; 1984 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Pending Trade Issues, 1954 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Prospects for Education and Employment, 1964 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - LWV Prospectus, 1980-1982 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - LWV Prospectus, 1982-1984 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - LWV Prospectus, 1984-1986 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Publications Catalog, LWV, 1959; 1983-1989 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Put Publications to Work, Undated (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Recreation and Parks: Case Studies in Local Program, 1962 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Report from The Hill, 1970-1971 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Report from The Hill, 1983-1985 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Report from The Hill, 1986-1987; 1990 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
    - School Survey Guide, 1961 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
    - "Simplified Parliamentary Procedure Based on Robert's Rules of Order", 1952 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Study and Action, LWV National Program, 1968-1972 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - The China Puzzle, 1967 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - "The League at 75: Looking Back - Looking Forward", Undated (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - The Politics of Trade, 1961; 1971 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - The United Nations: A Candid Appraisal, Booklet and Brochures, 1956; 1959; 1978 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Tips on Reaching the Public, 1953 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - USA Series, 1951; 1953 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - U.S. Foreign Trade Policy, 1776-1955, 1954 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - "Voter Registration Guide", 1992 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - When You Write to Washington: A Guide for Member Action Including Congressional Directory, 1969-1970; 1975-1976 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
    - With Continued Support..., 1959; 1966 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
    - World Economic Development: Our Part in a Common Effort, 1959 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
    - World Trade Affects You, Undated (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
    - You and Your National Government, 1962; 1977 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
    - 30 Years in Action: History of the State Program, 1952 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
    - State Board Reports, 1970 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
    - State Board Reports, 1971 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
    - State Board Reports, 1977 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
    - State Board Reports, 1978; 1981 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
    - State Board Reports, 1994; 1998 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Citizens Information Service, Undated (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Financing Education, 1965-1997 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Getting Into Issues: Your Guide to the 1996 Elections (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Getting Something Done: Political Effectiveness and Conference Techniques, 1966 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Hazardous Waste Information Focus on New York State, 1986 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Impact on Issues in New York State, 1997-2001 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 45)
    - In League in New York State: A Guide to Managing Local Leagues, 1994-1996 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Inner City Citizen Education Project, Newsletter, 1968 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Judiciary, Brochures, Undated (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Know Your Schools, 1974 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 49)
    - The Legislative Forecast, 1953; 1955; 1957 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 50)
    - The Legislative Forecast, 1958-1963 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 51)
    - The Legislative Review, 1956-1957 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 52)
    - The Legislative Review, 1958; 1960-1963 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Local Board Kit, 1977 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste in New York State, 1990 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Local Program Handbook, 1966 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 56)
    - "Management Newsbrief 5"and "Management Newsbrief", 1979; 1980 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Narcissa Cox Vanderlip: Chairman, New York State League of Women Voters, 1919-1923; 1982 (Box 31 (7-Publications), Folder 58)
    - New York State: A Citizen's Handbook, 1963; 1974 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - The New York State Voter, 1960-1962 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - The New York State Voter, 1963-1965 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - The New York State Voter, 1966-1967 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - The New York State Voter, 1969-1971 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - The New York State Voter, 1972-1974 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - The New York State Voter, 1975-1987 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - The New York State Voter, 1988-1999 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Publications Catalog, 1966-1967; 1984-1996 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - "Remember the Pride and the Passion: A Play in Four Acts", 1990 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Seeds of Failure: A Political Review of New York State's 1967 Constitutional Convention, 1973 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - L.W.V. State News, 1952-1955 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - L.W.V. State News, 1956-1960 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
    - The Citizen Lobbyist: A Guide to Action in the State Capital, 1976; 1993; 1997 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
    - The Health Care Puzzle in New York State: A Citizen Guide, 1985 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - The Road to the Voting Booth: A Handbook on Candidates Forums, 1985 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Toward an Evaluation of the Property Tax System in New York State, 1979 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Publications by Other Organizations, 1938-1999; 7.3
    - Acid Rain, 1984 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Acid Rain, 1984-1986 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Adirondacks, 1962 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Albany Guides, 1966; Undated (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - American Society for Public Administration, 1965-1968 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Bicentennial of U.S. Constitution Ratification, 1988 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - "Brush High School Today" LWV of South Euclid, 1959 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1998 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Capital Region, 1996 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Civil Rights, 1961; 1965 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Community Development Planning, 1960; 1963 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Congressional Elections, 1952; 1965; 1978 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
    - District Courts, 1967 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Economic Opportunity, 1964; 1965 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 31-32)
    - Education in New York State, 1959-1961 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Education for Employment, 1963; 1964 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Energy, 1981; 1990 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Energy, 1990-1992 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Environment, Magazine Clippings, 1984; 1989-1990 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Environment, 1966; 1991-1997 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Environment, 1996 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Environment, Newsletters, 1995-1997 (Box 32 (7-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Environment, Book, 1995 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Federal Budget, 1954; 1977; 1983 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Financing Education, 1957; 1959-1961 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Financing Education, 1979-1982 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Financing Education, 1994-1996 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Financing Education, 1995-1997 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Financing Education, 1996 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Foreign Economic Development, 1959-1961; 1969 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Foreign Policy Association Headline Series, 1958-1959 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Foreign Policy Association Headline Series, 1960-1961; 1972; 1984 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Fund for Modern Courts, 1980 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Garbage, Magazine, 1989-1990 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Great Decisions, 1973-1974; 1987; 1990; 1997 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Guide to Policy Making, 1998 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Household Hazardous Waste, 1982 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Housing in Albany, 1954 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Incinerators, 1988 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Incineration Book, 1989 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Innovations in American Government, 1997 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Intergovernmental Relations, 1970 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - International Development, 1951 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - International Trade, 1953; 1959; 1972 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Irrigation, 1957 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, Undated (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Municipal Government, 1965 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Mutual Security Program, 1959; 1960 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - New York State Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1938 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 33 (7-Publications), Folder 29-30)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - New York State Education Law, 1962 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - New York State Election Law, 1968 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - New York State Election Law, 1971 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - New York State Government, 1958; 1966; Undated (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - New York State History, 1974; Undated (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - New York State Impeachment Law, 1986 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - New York State Judiciary, 1997; 1999 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - New York State Legislative Forum, Brochure, 1982 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
    - New York State Legislature Guide, 1995 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
    - New York State Legislature, 1997; 1998 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Nomination and Election of the President, 1968 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Ozone, 1988-1992 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Party Politics, 1990 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Planning Public Libraries, 1957; Undated (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Population Growth, 1997 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Poverty, 1964 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Property Taxes, 1957; 1960; 1961 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Property Taxes, 1978-1980 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Recycling, 1987-1991 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Recycling, 1988-1990 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Recycling, Brochures, Undated (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Recycling and Incineration, Book, 1990 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Rockefeller Institute, 1992; 1998 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Rockefeller Institute, 1998-1999 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Separation of Church and State, 1997 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Social Services in New York State, 1974 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Solid Waste Management, Book, 1989 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Solid Waste Management, 1990 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Solid Waste Management, Composting, 1990 (Box 34 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Solid Waste Management, Composting, 1991 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Solid Waste Management, Cornell Waste Management Institute, 1989-1992 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Solid Waste Management, Newsletters and Brochures, 1981-1996 (not inclusive) (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Solid Waste Management, Reports, 1990; 1991 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Trade, 1970-1973 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - United Nations, 1953; 1973 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - United Nations, 1980; 1986; 1989 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - United Nations Publications, 1981 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Water Resources in New York State, 1962; 1963 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Water Resources in New York State, 1965; 1966 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Water Resources in New York State, 1966; 1967 (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Water Resources in New York State, 1983-1988 (not inclusive) (Box 35 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - The Albany Liberator, 1967 (Oversized 3)
    - The Legislative Gazett e, 50th Anniversary of Legislative Conference, LVWAC Special Section, 1988 (Oversized 3)
- Photographs and Scrapbooks, 1956-2000; 8; 2.61 cubic ft.